

PROFILE

Hard-working and dedicated student with over 5 years of work experience in the customer service industry. Eagerly seeking to use proven skills to help your company not only meet but exceed its goals. Frequently praised as diligent and reliable by my superiors, I guarantee to be an asset to your company.

CONTACT



PHONE: (816)-599-0102



EMAIL: gdstrehlow@outlook.com



ADDRESS: 5801 NW 63rd Street, Apt. 7100 Kansas City, MO 64151

SKILLS

- Problem solving
- Leadership
- Teamwork
- Critical thinking

Grant Strehlow

EDUCATION

Grand Canyon University

2019 - Present

Currently studying Finance and Economics, I anticipate graduating in the fall of 2022. My freshman year I was involved in intramural basketball as well as Esports. I have received multiple scholarships during my time at GCU for both my academics and involvement. I take my schooling very seriously and have upheld a 3.5 GPA thus far, placing me on the Dean's List for three consecutive semesters.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Chick-Fil-A (Cashier/Food Handler)

2015 - 2018, 2019, 2020

- Processed and filled customer orders with quick and accurate precision leading to a promotion within my first year
- Delivered prompt, friendly customer service helping to improve customer relations on a daily basis
- Assisted with stocking and restocking alongside cleaning duties, contributing to an overall positive store atmosphere
- Operated cash register with high efficiency never incurring a shortage or surplus in the drawer at routine checks

Nickel and Suede (Production Team Member)

2020 / March-September

- Received, organized, and sorted incoming shipments
- Performed production duties including picking, packing, shipping, counting, record keeping, assembling, and cleaning
- Operated heavy machinery to cut and emboss leather

Best Buy (Customer Service Specialist)

2018 - 2019

- Built and maintained relationships with customers
- Led customer service operations such as: returns/exchanges, telephone calls, check-out, et al.
- Marketed special offers and sales to customers

Discount Tire (Technician)

Summer 2018

- Performed tire rotations, flat tire repairs, and changing heavy duty tires
- Organized merchandise and maintained warehouse cleanliness